

Personal Data:

Jagoda Bieniek

Adress:

Street Langiewicza

30/5

31-425 Kraków

Phone:

+ 48 533 261 323

E-mail:

jagoda.bieniek1234@gmail .com

Skills:

JavaScript (ES5/ES6)
TypeScript

JavaScript Frameworks:

React, Angular, Vue, jQuery, Anime, Jasmine, JEST.

Bootstrap 4.0

RWD

CSS3/SASS

HTML5

REST

WEBPACK

SQL/NoSQL

JAVA

SharePoint

Unix systems

Profil

Since 2018 professionally and privately i have being engaged to creation and development of web applications, mainly dealing with Front-end web development. The main technologies which I use are: React, Angular i Vue, HTML 5, CSS (preprocessor SASS). In 2020, to develop my knowledge, I started my studies in the field of Web Application Programming.

Employment History

System Engineer (BPM developer) at Aptiv, Kraków

December 2020 - Now

- Design, development and maintenance of user interfaces in IBM Business Process business process management tool Management.
- Creating new functionalities mainly using JavaScript (Angular), Bootstrap and the use of SQL queries.
- Conducting tests of implemented solutions

Junior SharePoint Engineer at SolidBrain, Kraków

August 2019 — November 2020

- Designing, developing and maintaining new features for SharePoint 2013 with strong focus on Front-End.
- Fixing existing application bugs
- Responsible for implementing user interface elements.
- Developing application components using JavaScript / TypeScript, HTML, CSS.
- Creating code solution which was implemented on different devices (mobile, desktop)
- Writing unit tests using for example Jasmine and Jest.

Application Specialist at SolidBrain, Kraków

December 2018 – July 2019

- Support and administration of SharePoint 2013.
- Collaboration with users from all over the world.
- Discussing and implementing user suggestions together with developers.
- Solving user problems as well as providing training on the application.
- Data and permission management.

Insurance Advisor at ABM Włodarczyk, Kraków

July 2017 – November 2018

- Consulting and sale of insurance products.
- Maintaining a customer database in accordance with GDPR standards.

Education

Web Application Programming – AGH, Kraków

October 2020 - now

Post-graduate study

Chemical Engineering – Politechnika Krakowska, Kraków

March 2016 – 2018 June

Master Degree (English Study)

Chemical Engineering – Politechnika Krakowska, Kraków

October 2012 – 2016 February

Belcher Degree